Archaeology just got badass!
Tomb Invader is a action, adventure, tv movie film directed by James Thomas.
Archaeologist Alabama Channing sets off to uncover the ancient tomb of Quin Shi
Haung, which promises riches and answers to family mysteries.
Alabama Channing, played by Gina Vitori.
Julie Channing, played by Tammy Klein.
Isabelle Villeneuve, played by Lindsay Sawyer.
Li Wei, played by John Wusah.
Helena, played by Samantha Bowling.
Nathan, played by Andrew J Katers.
Lara Croft: Tomb Raider is a 2001 action adventure film based on the Tomb Raider video
game series featuring the character Lara Croft, portrayed by Angelina Jolie.
An international co-production between the United States, Canada, United Kingdom, Japan and Germany, it was directed by Simon
West and revolves around Lara Croft trying to obtain ancient artifacts in competition with the Illuminati.
The film was released on June 15, 2001, to mostly negative reviews from
critics, although Jolie was praised for her performance.
It grossed $274.7 million worldwide, making it  one of the
highest-grossing video game adaptations.
A sequel, Lara Croft: Tomb Raider – The Cradle of Life, was released in 2003.
The film explores themes of china, billionaire, archaeologist, tomb, booby trap.